[{
    "questionType": "one",
    "questionText": "Why is AWS more economical than traditional data centers for application with varying compute workloads?",
    "options": ["Amazon EC2 costs are billed on a monthly basis.",
      "Users retain full administrative access to their Amazon EC2 instance.",
      "Amazon EC2 instances can be launched on demand when needed.",
      "Users can permanently run enough instances to handle peak workloads."
      ],
    "correct": [2],
    "resource": "r'https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/'"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "one",
    "questionText": "Which AWS service would simplify the migration of a database to AWS?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Storage Gateway",
      "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)",
      "Amazon EC2",
      "Amazon AppStream 2.0"
    ],
    "correct": [1],
    "resource": "https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "three",
    "questionText": "AWS uses the shared responsibility model. For security, which of the following are the responsibilities of AWS? Choose 3",
    "options": [
      "User password rules",
      "Configure Security Groups",
      "Physically securing compute resources",
      "Network patching",
      "Disk disposal"
    ],
    "correct": [0, 0, 1, 1, 1],
    "resource": "https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "two",
    "questionText": "Upon venturing into using the AWS Cloud, your company decides to follow the 5 pillars of the AWS Well Architected Framework. Which items are pillars of the Well Architected Framework? Choose 2",
    "options": [
      "Scalability",
      "Operational Excellence",
      "Elasticity",
      "Ease of Use",
      "Reliability"
    ],
    "correct": [0, 1, 0, 0, 1],
    "resource": "https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/"
  },
   {
    "questionType": "one",
    "questionText": "Under the shared responsibility model, which of the following is the customer responsible for?",
    "options": [
      "Ensuring that disk drives are wiped after use.",
      "Ensuring that firmware is updated on hardware devices.",
      "Ensuring that data is encrypted at rest.",
      "Ensuring that network cables are category six or higher."
    ],
    "correct": [2],
    "resource": "https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "two",
    "questionText": "Which AWS characteristics make AWS cost effective for a workload with dynamic user demand? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "High availability",
      "Elasticity",
      "Shared security model",
      "Pay-as-you-go pricing",
      "Reliability"
    ],
    "correct": [0, 1, 0, 1, 0],
    "resource": "https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "one",
    "questionText": "Which of the following Amazon EC2 pricing models allow customers to use existing server-bound software licenses?",
    "options": [
      "Spot Instances",
      "Reserved Instances",
      "On-Demand Instances",
      "Dedicated Hosts"
    ],
    "correct": [3],
    "resource": "https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "one",
    "questionText": "Which of the following inspects AWS environments to find opportunities that can save money for users and also improve system performance?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Cost Explorer",
      "AWS Trusted Advisor",
      "Consolidated billing",
      "Detailed billing"
    ],
    "correct": [1],
    "resource": "https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "two",
    "questionText": "Which AWS services can host a Microsoft SQL Server database? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "Amazon S3",
      "Amazon Redshift",
      "Amazon Aurora",
      "Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)",
      "Amazon EC2"
    ],
    "correct": [0, 0, 0, 1, 1],
    "resource": "https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "one",
    "questionText": "Distributing workloads across multiple Availability Zones supports which cloud architecture design principle?",
    "options": [
      "Implement automation.",
      "Design for agility.",
      "Design for failure.",
      "Implement elasticity."
    ],
    "correct": [2],
    "resource": "https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "one",
    "questionText": "A customer would like to design and build a new workload on AWS Cloud but does not have the AWS-related software technical expertise in-house. Which of the following AWS programs can a customer take advantage of to achieve that outcome?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Partner Network Technology Partners",
      "AWS Marketplace",
      "AWS Partner Network Consulting Partners",
      "AWS Service Catalog"
    ],
    "correct": [2],
    "resource": "https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "one",
    "questionText": "What AWS team assists customers with accelerating cloud adoption through paid engagements in any of several specialty practice areas?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Enterprise Support",
      "AWS Professional Services",
      "AWS Solutions Architects",
      "AWS Account Managers"
    ],
    "correct": [1],
    "resource": "https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "one",
    "questionText": "Which service stores objects, provides real-time access to those objects, and offers versioning and lifecycle capabilities?",
    "options": [
      "Amazon Glacier",
      "AWS Storage Gateway",
      "Amazon S3",
      "Amazon EBS"
    ],
    "correct": [2],
    "resource": "https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "one",
    "questionText": "The use of what AWS feature or service allows companies to track and categorize spending on a detailed level?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Budgets",
      "Consolidated billing",
      "AWS Marketplace",
      "Cost allocation tags"
    ],
    "correct": [3],
    "resource": "https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "one",
    "questionText": "Compared with costs in traditional and virtualized data centers, AWS has:",
    "options": [
      "lower variable costs and lower upfront costs.",
      "fixed usage costs and lower upfront costs.",
      "lower variable costs and greater upfront costs.",
      "greater variable costs and greater upfront costs."
    ],
    "correct": [0],
    "resource": "https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "one",
    "questionText": "Which of the following Reserved Instance (RI) pricing models provides the highest average savings compared to On-Demand pricing?",
    "options": [
      "Three-year, No Upfront, Convertible RI pricing",
      "Three-year, All Upfront, Standard RI pricing",
      "One-year, No Upfront, Standard RI pricing",
      "One-year, All Upfront, Convertible RI pricing"
    ],
    "correct": [1],
    "resource": "https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "two",
    "questionText": "Which of the following are advantages of AWS consolidated billing? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "The ability to receive one bill for multiple accounts",
      "Potential volume discounts, as usage in all accounts is combined",
      "Service limits increasing by default in all accounts",
      "A fixed discount on the monthly bill",
      "The automatic extension of the master account's AWS support plan to all accounts"
    ],
    "correct": [1, 1, 0, 0, 0],
    "resource": "https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "three",
    "questionText": "Which AWS tools assist with estimating costs? (Choose three.)",
    "options": [
      "Detailed billing report",
      "Cost allocation tags",
      "AWS Simple Monthly Calculator",
      "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator",
      "Cost Estimator"
    ],
    "correct": [0, 1, 1, 1, 0],
    "resource": "https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "one",
    "questionText": "Which of the following is a correct relationship between regions, Availability Zones, and edge locations?",
    "options": [
      "Data centers contain regions.",
      "Regions contain Availability Zones.",
      "Availability Zones contain edge locations.",
      "Edge locations contain regions."
    ],
    "correct": [1],
    "resource": "https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "one",
    "questionText": "A company is considering using AWS for a self-hosted database that requires a nightly shutdown for maintenance and cost-saving purposes. Which service should the company use?",
    "options": [
      "Amazon EC2 with Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)",
      "Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) with Amazon EC2 instance store",
      "Amazon DynamoDB",
      "Amazon Redshift"
    ],
    "correct": [0],
    "resource": "https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "one",
    "questionText": "What costs are included when comparing AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) with on-premises TCO?",
    "options": [
      "Project management",
      "Antivirus software licensing",
      "Data center security",
      "Software development"
    ],
    "correct": [3],
    "resource": "https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "two",
    "questionText": "Which services can be used across hybrid AWS Cloud architectures? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "Elastic Block Storage",
      "Virtual Private Gateway",
      "Elastic File System",
      "Amazon ElasticMapReduce",
      "Amazon CloudTrail"
    ],
    "correct": [0, 1, 1, 0, 0],
    "resource": "https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "two",
    "questionText": "Which of the following are characteristics of Amazon S3? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "A global file system",
      "An object store",
      "A local file store",
      "A network file system",
      "Cannot be shared among application"
    ],
    "correct": [1, 1, 0, 0, 0],
    "resource": "https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "one",
    "questionText": "Which service enables risk auditing by continuously monitoring and logging account activity, including user actions in the AWS Management Console and AWS SDKs?",
    "options": [
      "Amazon CloudWatch",
      "AWS CloudTrail",
      "AWS Config",
      "AWS Health"
    ],
    "correct": [1],
    "resource": "https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html"
  }
]